eastcoastdaily.in 2018-05-19

# Privacy Policy - East Coast Daily |

Eastcoast operates Website services, Messaging services, Video services, Audio services, Internet services, Mobile services and other Allied services offered from time to time. The privacy policy describes collection and use of user’s personal information (Details of person with email address) and non personal information (User interests and site usage). This is applicable to all users that is users utilizing its services of eastcoast services with or without registration.

**Information submitted by users**

Members who voluntarily submit all personal information at its time of registration with eastcoast services will come within the definition of submitted information.

**Information Collected**

Eastcoast will endeavor to gather information about the visitors by the IP address, browser type, other software and hardware information. We will use cookies and other trading technologies for the collection of data and information. Clubbing of information collected with information furnished by you will be move only after your consent.

**Information on usage**

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**Change of Privacy Policy**

Our privacy policy may be changed at any time by posting a revised privacy policy which will be effective as and when posted in our website. Users are required to review the website and privacy policy to understand the periodical changes.
